http://www.earthtimes.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Our visitors privacy is important to us here at The Earth Times and it is important that all visitors are aware of the personal data being collected from them.
What information does The Earth Times collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.
When registering on our site for member services, newsletters or to post comments, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.
Google: As a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet (interest based advertising). Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Other advertising networks information and opt out: The Earth Times may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services deemed of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about opting out and not having this information passed on please visit the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We never ask for any of your private financial information or details (credit cards, social security numbers, financial details etc) The Earth Times will never ask for this information from you.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
